<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<interactive>
  <settings>
    <instructions>Answer the following questions to show how to use PowerPoint to conduct each activity.</instructions>
    <css>
      <width>700</width>
      <height>400</height>
    </css>
  </settings>
<question>
    <type>mc</type>
   <title>PowerPoint Skills</title>
    <quiz>How do you search for and add an online image to a PowerPoint slide?</quiz>
    <answer>Go to the Insert tab and select Online Pictures from the Images group.</answer>
    <correct>It's obvious you paid attention to the lesson! You know how to search and insert online images.</correct>
    <option> Go to the View tab and view images to use in a PowerPoint.</option>
    <feedback>Trying is like exercising your brain.</feedback>
    <option>Go to the Page Layout tab and adjust the theme.</option>
    <feedback>Be proud of your effort on this question, but try again. You will increase your brain strength if you do!</feedback>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
  </question>

<question>       <type>mc</type> <title>PowerPoint Skills</title>

<quiz>What is the most effective way to represent the process of writing a research paper?</quiz>
    <answer>Use SmartArt to illustrate the steps.</answer>
    <correct>You made the connection! SmartArt is a great way to show the process of writing a research paper.</correct>
    <option>Add an image of a library.</option>
    <feedback>Good effort! A picture of a library doesn't show the research writing process, though.</feedback>
 <option>Tell a story of when you have written an essay.</option>
    <feedback>Your brain gets stronger every time you try! Think a little more about this one.</feedback>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
  </question>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type> <title>PowerPoint Skills</title>

    <quiz>What type of image would best support a presentation on the dangers of distracted driving?</quiz>
    <answer>A picture of a car crash</answer>
    <correct>Sad but true. An image that shows a possible consequence of distracted driving powerfully supports the message of the presentation.</correct>
    <option>A picture of a new car</option>
      <feedback>Effort is spinach for the brain. Think about this more and really flex your thinking muscles.</feedback>
    <option>A picture of traffic </option>
    <feedback>You are on the right track, but there is a better option to support the presentation on distracted driving.</feedback>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>

  </question>
   <question>
    <type>mc</type> <title>PowerPoint Skills</title>

    <quiz>Which tab do you use to add images, shapes, SmartArt, symbols, and text boxes to a slide?</quiz>
    <answer>Insert </answer>
    <correct>Your thinking cap looks good on you. Way to go!</correct>
    <option>File </option>
       <feedback>This is a worthy effort.</feedback>
    <option>Home</option>
       <feedback>Your brain gets more muscular with each attempt!</feedback>
       <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>

  </question>
</interactive>
