<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<interactive>
  <settings>
    <instructions>Read the following scenarios and show how you would use the internet to perform email
      activities.</instructions>
    <css>
      <width>700</width>
      <height>400</height>
    </css>

  </settings>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type>
    <title>Expert or Apprentice?</title>
    <quiz>Your boss asks you to send her the documents she needs for a critical meeting with important clients
      downtown. She said she needs them like yesterday. What do you do?</quiz>
    <answer>Compose an email and use the Insert button to add the files as attachments.</answer>
    <option>Hire a bike messenger to hand-deliver the document.</option>
    <option>Send the documents through the U.S. Postal Service.</option>
    <option>Walk them. After all, she is right down the hall.</option>
    <correct>Great thinking! Email is fast, safe, and can be accessed through any number of devices.</correct>
    <feedback>Hmmm. That could get expensive.</feedback>
    <feedback>Yikes! What if the post office loses the documents?</feedback>
    <feedback>What if your boss is not in her office?</feedback>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
    <tries>2</tries>
  </question>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type>
    <title>Expert or Apprentice?</title>
    <quiz>A colleague sent you an awesome article about using proper ergonomics while sitting at the computer. You
      don't have time to read the article now, but you would like to save it for future reference. What is the
      best way to do this?</quiz>
    <answer>Select the article attachment and save it to your computer.</answer>
    <option>Print it.</option>
    <option>Reply to the email and ask your colleague to resend the article next week.</option>
    <option>Take a screenshot with your phone.</option>
    <correct>Awesome answer! You can access it later and save money and natural resources.</correct>
    <feedback>Money doesn't grow on trees! Printing uses ink and paper, both of which get expensive.</feedback>
    <feedback>Think of a different option that will be more time-efficient for you and your colleague.</feedback>
    <feedback>Screenshots certainly have their place in capturing information, but they are not effective for long
      articles.
    </feedback>
    <failed>With more effort, you can answer correctly next time.</failed>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
    <tries>2</tries>
  </question>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type>
    <title>Expert or Apprentice?</title>
    <quiz>You are working on a project and would like to get all the members together face-to-face to collaborate.
      What is the best approach?</quiz>
    <answer>Create a new calendar event and add attendees.</answer>
    <correct>Way to go! You obviously see this method is efficient and will help you and attendees manage your busy
      schedules.</correct>
    <failed>With more effort, you can answer correctly next time.</failed>
    <option>Use Word online to create a meeting notice and send as an email attachment.</option>
    <feedback>Double-booking is like double-dipping. No one likes it! Think of another option that will give a good
      view of your schedule.</feedback>
    <option>Post your meeting to Facebook.</option>
    <feedback>Uh oh! Did you ever send the new intern a friend request?</feedback>
    <option>Send an invitation. People appreciate getting real mail and not just junk.</option>
    <feedback>True, but this method has downfalls. I hope everyone adds it to their planner!</feedback>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
    <tries>2</tries>
  </question>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type>
    <title>Expert or Apprentice?</title>
    <quiz>Working for a large company, you seem to meet new people each day. What is the best way to manage all your
      associates’ contact information?</quiz>
    <answer>Use the People app to add names, email addresses, phone numbers, etc.</answer>
    <correct>Now that is using your noggin! The People app is an effective way to manage your contacts.</correct>
    <failed>With more effort, you can answer correctly next time.</failed>
    <option>Use a three-ring binder with plastic business card inserts.</option>
    <feedback>This was awesome in the 80s. Try to think of a method that uses 21st century technology.</feedback>
    <option>Start a running list using Word Online. Each new entry will automatically number itself.</option>
    <feedback>The numbering feature is nifty, but there is a more efficient and effective method.</feedback>
    <option>Ask associates to text you, so you can program them into your phone.</option>
    <feedback>Asking the CEO to text you is not terribly professional.</feedback>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
    <tries>2</tries>
  </question>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type>
    <title>Expert or Apprentice?</title>
    <quiz>On a daily basis, you receive at least 10 new emails. How can you best organize your messages?</quiz>
    <answer>Drag messages to existing and new folders.</answer>
    <correct>Yep! Great thinking. This is a filing system to organize your email messages for future reference.</correct>
    <failed>With more effort, you can answer correctly next time.</failed>
    <option>Keep all emails in your inbox.</option>
    <feedback>The saying "The more the merrier" is not an effective way to manage your messages.</feedback>
    <option>Delete all emails after you read them.</option>
    <feedback>Uh, this will keep your inbox tidy, but it's not great for people without a photographic memory. Try
      again.</feedback>
    <option>Check your messages on Mondays and Thursdays.</option>
    <feedback>Scheduling your tasks is a good idea, but this won't solve organization issues.</feedback>
    <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
    <tries>2</tries>
  </question>
</interactive>
