<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<interactive>
  <settings>
    <instructions>Review the following charts and graphs. Select the option that best reflects what is being communicated.</instructions>
    <css>
      <width>700</width>
      <height>400</height>
    </css>
  </settings>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type>
    <title>title-image?</title>
    <quiz>What is the purpose of this line graph? </quiz>
    <answer>To show how many happy and sad emoticons are tweeted per hour in the UK.</answer>
    <correct>Awesome attention to detail! You read the graph heading carefully and identified the correct message of the data.</correct>
    <option>To show how many people in the UK are happy versus sad. </option>
     <feedback>You’re on the right track, but pay closer attention to all the details in the graph heading. Try again.</feedback> <option>To show how many people in the UK use Twitter.</option>
  
    <feedback>You can do this, so don't give up! Go back and re-read the graph heading to review all the details.</feedback>
  </question>

<question>       <type>mc</type>
<title>title? image?</title>
    <quiz>According to this "pie" chart, which type of pie is most popular?</quiz>
    <answer>Pumpkin</answer>
    <correct>Pumpkin is the fan favorite! Good job identifying the largest slice of pie on the "pie" chart.</correct>
    <option>Apple</option>
    <feedback>Apple pie is yummy, but look again at the size of the pies. Which one is the largest?</feedback>
 <option>Pecan</option>
       <feedback>Pecan pie is ooey, gooey, and delicious. But it is not the favorite. Try again.</feedback>
  </question>
  <question>
    <type>mc</type>
    <title>image?</title>
    <quiz>Which month had the least amount of French fry consumption?</quiz>
    <answer>February</answer>
    <correct>It looks like people are taking their New Year's resolutions seriously and staying away from the fries. Good job!</correct>
    <option>April</option>
    <feedback>People were pretty good about avoiding fries in April, but there is a month people were even better. Try again!</feedback>
    <option>September</option>
    <feedback>Wow! Was there a special on French fries this month? Look again at for the month with the smallest French fry consumption.</feedback>
  
  </question>
 
</interactive>
