<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<interactive>
    <settings>
        <instructions>Answer the following questions to show how to use PowerPoint to conduct each activity.
        </instructions>
        <css>
            <width>700</width>
            <height>550</height>
        </css>
    </settings>
    <question>
        <type>mc</type>
        <title><![CDATA[ &nbsp; ]]></title>
        <quiz>
            <![CDATA[ <img src="images/hardread_nk.jpg" alt=" Image of PowerPoint slide with a blue background and red text."> <br>]]>
            What is one way to fix the clarity?
        </quiz>
        <answer>Make the text color lighter, like white or light gray.</answer>
        <correct>Awesome thinking! Light colors show up clearly on dark backgrounds.</correct>
        <option>Add a relevant picture.</option>
        <feedback>Images add visual interest, but they do not make text appear clearer.
        </feedback>
        <option>Use a different font style.</option>
        <feedback>Changing the font style won't make the text appear clearer. Can you think of something in this lesson
            that solves clarity problems?
        </feedback>
        <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>
    </question>

    <question>
        <type>mc</type>
        <title><![CDATA[ &nbsp; ]]></title>

        <quiz>A student is creating a PowerPoint presentation to explain her scientific experiment and its results to
            her teacher and classmates. Which theme below is most appropriate for this purpose?
        </quiz>
        <answer>
            <![CDATA[ <img src="images/purpleppt_nk.jpg"  alt="Image is a PowerPoint slide with a deep purple background and a narrow vertical bar at the top right-hand corner.">]]></answer>
        <correct>Your hat size is increasing because your brain is growing! This slide has style, yet it is also
            streamlined, making it more appropriate for academic purposes.
        </correct>
        <option>
            <![CDATA[ <img src="images/prettyppt_nk.jpg"  alt="Image of a PowerPoint slide that has a blue floral theme.">]]></option>
        <feedback>This theme is pretty, but ask yourself whether it's appropriate for academic purposes.
        </feedback>
        <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>

    </question>
    <question>
        <type>mc</type>
        <title><![CDATA[ &nbsp; ]]></title>
        <quiz>A baby food company is creating a PowerPoint to present a new product to a focus group of mothers. Which
            variant is most appropriate for the purpose and audience?
        </quiz>
        <answer>Light yellow</answer>
        <correct>Great thinking! Light yellow is a gender-neutral color, and it is soft and happy (like a lot of
            babies).
        </correct>
        <option>Dark red</option>
        <feedback>Each time you try, you exercise your brain. Think about what the color red typically represents and
            evaluate if it is effective for the product and audience.
        </feedback>
        <option>Deep purple</option>
        <feedback>Your brain gets stronger when you think. Contemplate what a "deep" color looks like and decide whether
            this supports the purpose and audience.
        </feedback>
        <failedTitle>That is also incorrect.</failedTitle>

    </question>
</interactive>
